Guide to the Yale School of Music Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1930-1983; Accession 1989-A-121
  - International Mailing Lists, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 822)
  - Yale - Letter to Faculty, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 823)
  - Blue Mailing List Forms, undated (Box 15, Folder 824)
  - Yale - Mailing List - Bell Lucas, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 825)
  - Regional Advertisements - East, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 826)
  - National Auditions - Newspaper Advertisement, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 827)
  - National Auditions - Magazine Advertisement, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 828)
  - National Auditions - Yale Alumni Advertisement, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 829)
  - Regional Advertisements - Auditions, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 830)
  - National Auditions - Regional Newspaper Ads, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 831)
  - Finished Advertisements, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 832)
  - Yale - Heading Repros, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 833)
  - Norfolk Advertisements, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 834)
  - Norfolk, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 835)
  - Norfolk Recruiting, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 836)
  - Yale Ads - Tear Sheets, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 837)
  - Norfolk Ads, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 838)
  - Norfolk Advertising, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 839)
  - Other Summer Music Festivals, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 840)
  - Norfolk Art Collection, undated, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 841)
  - Norfolk: Road Signs, undated (Box 15, Folder 842)
  - Norfolk Historical Society, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 843)
  - Norfolk Mailers pre '72, undated 1969 (Box 15, Folder 844)
  - Norfolk Art School, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 845)
  - Yale - AAA Tour Book, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 846)
  - Yale - New England Innkeepers Association, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 847)
  - Yale - Rand McNally, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 848)
  - Norfolk Editorials, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 849)
  - Yale - The H. M. Gous:ha Company, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 850)
  - Yale - Associated Restaurants of Connecticut, undated (Box 15, Folder 851)
  - Yale - Connecticut Committee on the Arts, undated (Box 15, Folder 852)
  - Connecticut Development Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 853)
  - Sanford Folder, 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 856)
  - Medallic Art Company, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 857)
  - Sanford Medal, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 858)
  - String Folder - String Faculty, 1972-1978 (Box 15, Folder 859)
  - Survey, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 860)
  - Glee Club, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 861)
  - Voice, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 862)
  - Type Proofs 8 pt., undated (Box 15, Folder 863)
  - Layouts and Stock Sample, undated (Box 15, Folder 864)
  - Type Proofs, undated (Box 15, Folder 865)
  - Literature Colleges - Other Schools, 1972-1979 (Box 15, Folder 866)
  - Norfolk - Posters, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 867)
  - Others' Publications, 1975-1979 (Box 15, Folder 868)
  - Yale at Norfolk: Recruiting, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 869)
  - Harper Materials, 1965-1968 (Box 15, Folder 870)
  - Yale - Schedules and Information, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 871)
  - Promotional Brochure, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 872)
  - Faculty Announcements, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 873)
  - Miscellaneous Literature, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 874)
  - Harper Ads, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 875)
  - National Auditions, 1971-1976 (Box 16, Folder 876)
  - Eastman, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 877)
  - Interlochen, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 878)
  - Publication Committee, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 879)
  - Music Cabinet, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 880)
  - Miscellanious Literature, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 881)
  - Other's Work, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 882)
  - Yale Publications for Reference, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 883)
  - Cincinnati Conservatory, undated (Box 16, Folder 884)
  - Other Schools Literature, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 885)
  - Juilliard, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 886)
  - Ellington: General Correspondence, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 887)
  - Ellington: Internal Correspondence, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 888)
  - Ellington Convocation October 14, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 889)
  - Dinner, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 890)
  - Hotel for October 14, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 892)
  - Ellington Medals, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 893)
  - Conservatory without Walls, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 894)
  - General Materials and Notes, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 895)
  - Miscellanious Letters, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 896)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 897)
  - Contract, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 898)
  - Chamber of Commerce List Press Conference and Reception September 21, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 899)
  - Requests for Checks, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 900)
  - Casual Payment Forms [see box 25], 1972 (Box 16, Folder 901)
  - Bills - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 902)
  - Burson Marsteller: Duke Ellington Fellowship Program, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 903)
  - Travel Arrangements, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 904)
  - Box Office Records - Yale Co-op - N.Y. Jazz Museum - N.H. Arena etc., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 905)
  - Burson-Marstellar Public Relations, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 906)
  - Inquiries for Mailing List, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 907)
  - Pullman, Christopher Program Brochure, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 908)
  - Recording, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 909)
  - W-TIC Video Tape, undated (Box 16, Folder 910)
  - Staging and Production, 1972-1977 (Box 16, Folder 911)
  - Ellington: Musicians' Address List [see box 25], 1972-1977 (Box 16, Folder 912)
  - Remodeling Study, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 913)
  - Index to Dean's Files, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 914)
  - AME at Ann Arbor (Association of Music Executives), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 915)
  - AME - Seven Springs Conference, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 916)
  - Seven Springs Conference, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 917)
  - NASM: Minnesota (National Association of Schools of Music), 1980 (Box 17, Folder 918)
  - NASN: Denver, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 919)
  - NASM: University of Miami Evaluation, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 920)
  - Tulane, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 921)
  - NASM: Northwestern, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 922)
  - NASM Evaluation, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 923)
  - Commission on Higher Education Middle States Association, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 924)
  - NASM - The Juillard Case, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 925)
  - Juilliard School, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 926)
  - NASM: Interlochen Evaluation, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 927)
  - YSM Alumni Day, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 928)
  - YSM Alumni convocation, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 929)
  - Alumni Association - Years Act., 1971 (Box 17, Folder 930)
  - Alumni Convocation, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 931)
  - YSM Alumni, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 932)
  - Afumni Weekend: October 17 and 18, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 933)
  - Afumni Association Minutes, 1955-1963 (Box 17, Folder 934)
  - Alumni Association, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 935)
  - Alumni Association, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 936)
  - Alumni Association, 1955-1972 (Box 17, Folder 937)
  - Advisory Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 938)
  - Advisement [see box 25], 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 939)
  - Registration Breakdown, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 940)
  - Performance Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 941)
  - Permanent Officers [see box 25], 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 942)
  - Music Executive Officers, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 943)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 944)
  - Norfolk - July, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 945)
  - University Council: Music committee, 1962-1968 (Box 18, Folder 946)
  - Hanes - July, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 947)
  - Hanes - December, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 948)
  - Yale golf Course, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 949)
  - Agenda Items, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 950)
  - Golf Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 951)
  - Executive Director - Yale Golf, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 952)
  - Golf Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 953)
  - General Information Relevant to Recruitment of Golf Director, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 954)
  - Job Interviews by Executive Director - Inactive [see box 25], 1974 (Box 18, Folder 955)
  - Yale Golf, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 956)
  - Yale Golf, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 957)
  - Yale Golf, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 958)
  - Golf, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 959)
  - Golf Committee - Supporting Documents, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 960)
  - Programs
    - 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 961)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 962)
    - Norfolk Programs, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 963)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 964)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 965)
    - Complete Set of Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 966)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 967)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 968)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 969)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 970)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 971)
    - 1973 (Box 20, Folder 972)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 973)
  - Programs and Literature, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 974)
  - Miscellaneous Architecteral Literature, undated (Box 20, Folder 975)
  - Scholarships and Prizes
    - H. Frank Bozyan Scholarship, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 977)
    - H. Frank Bozyan Scholarship, 1967-1972 (Box 21, Folder 978)
    - Bradley-Keeler Memorial Scholarship, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 979)
    - Woods Chandler Prize, 1936-1970 (Box 21, Folder 980)
    - Charles Finch Dalton Memorial, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 982)
    - Electronic Music Studio Gifts, 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 984)
    - Harriet G. Fox Prize, 1928-1955 (Box 21, Folder 985)
    - Rena Greenwald Memorial Prize, 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 987)
    - Ellsworth Grumman Scholarship, 1965-1977 (Box 21, Folder 988)
    - Nowland Memorial Prize, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 990)
    - Elias Howland Prize - Stokowski, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 991)
    - George Knight Houpt Memorial, 1927-37 (Box 21, Folder 993)
    - John D. Jackson Prize, 1943-1970 (Box 21, Folder 994)
    - Benjamin Jepson Prize, 1966-1973 (Box 21, Folder 995)
    - Harry B. Jepson Memorial Scholarsip, 1942-1962 (Box 21, Folder 996)
    - Frances Kellogg Prize, 1930-1973 (Box 21, Folder 997)
    - Julia Abigail Lockwood Scholarship, 1943-1955 (Box 21, Folder 999)
    - Mattatuck Musical Arts, 1949-1964 (Box 21, Folder 1000)
    - Miscellaneous Gifts, 1958-1973 (Box 21, Folder 1003)
    - Henry and Amanda Noss Prize, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 1006)
    - Horatio Parker Memorial, 1945-1973 (Box 21, Folder 1007)
    - School of Music Scholarship, 1955-1970 (Box 21, Folder 1011)
    - Julia R. Sherman Prize, 1938-1970 (Box 21, Folder 1012)
    - Julia Silliman Memorial, 1927-1941 (Box 21, Folder 1013)
    - Bruce Simonds Scholarship, 1960-1972 (Box 21, Folder 1014)
    - David Stanley Smith Scholarship, 1952-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1015)
  - Commencement, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1018)
  - Tapp Scholarship, 1962-1968 (Box 21, Folder 1019)
  - Emma Phipps White Memorial Scholarship, 1968-1972 (Box 21, Folder 1021)
  - Keith Wilson Wind Instrument Student Scholarship, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1022)
  - Faculty Steering Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1023)
  - Music Executive Committee, 1971-1979 (Box 21, Folder 1024)
  - Music Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1025)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1026)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 1027)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 1028)
  - MMA Orals, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1030)
  - MMA Admissions - Dean Nelson, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1031)
  - Proposed Budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1032)
  - Music Educators National Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1033)
  - Budget Letters, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1034)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1035)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1036)
  - Norfolk Planning, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1037)
  - CONE (Chamber Orchestra of New England), 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1038)
  - To Discuss: Provost [see box 25], 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1039)
  - Thurston and Auld, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1040)
  - Academic Information, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1041)
  - Faculty Openings Fall, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1042)
  - Steering Committee [see box 25], 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1043)
  - Meetings - Faculty and Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1044)
  - Faculty Resumes, requested, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1045)
  - [Letter to M. Brooks], 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1047)
  - Steering Committee [see box 25]
    - 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 1048)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 1049)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1050)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1051)
  - Faculty Meetings
    - 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1052)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 1053)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 1054)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 1055)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1056)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 1057)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 1058)
  - Performance Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1059)
  - Performance Committee, 1975-1983 (Box 22, Folder 1060)
  - Music Buildings: Design - Equipment, 1959-1967 (Box 22, Folder 1061)
  - Music Buildings Brochures, undated (Box 22, Folder 1062)
  - Cleveland Institute, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1063)
  - Fredonia, undated (Box 22, Folder 1064)
  - Juilliard, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1065)
  - Oberlin, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1066)
  - Toronto, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1067)
  - University of Iowa, undated (Box 22, Folder 1068)
  - Illinois, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1069)
  - New Music Center, 1973-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1070)
  - Music Center, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1071)
  - Music Buildings: Space Requirement, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1073)
  - Catalogs from Various Schools; Architectural Literature, undated (Box 22, Folder 1074)
  - Miscellaneous Architectural Literature SEE BOX 20 FOLDER 1004, undated (Box 22, Folder 1075)
  - Catalogs From Various Schools, undated (Box 23, Folder 1076)
  - Architectural Literature, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1077)
  - Architectural Literature, undated (Box 23, Folder 1078)
  - Music Center Architectural Matters, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1079)
  - School of Music - Auditoriums, etc., 1964-1968 (Box 23, Folder 1080)
  - New Music Center - Yale Plans, 1958-1969 (Box 23, Folder 1081)
  - Building Plans Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 1082)
  - Lists, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1083)
  - Building Design Program for Proposed Music Center, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1084)
  - Music Buildings, Rooms and Equipment, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1085)
  - Music Center Corporation Documents, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1086)
  - Hendrie Hall, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1087)
  - Woolsey Hall, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1088)
  - New Music Center Prospective Architects, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1089)
  - Purcell Noppe Associates, Inc., 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1090)
  - Architecture in various places (music auditoriums), undated (Box 23, Folder 1091)
  - West Coast Trip, 1973 December 9-14 (Box 23, Folder 1092)
  - Restricted Folders from the collection, previously inventoried (Box 24)
  - Restricted Folders from the collection, previously inventoried (Box 25)
  - YSM Reports, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1093)
  - Advertisements, 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1094)
  - Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1095)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1096)
  - Music at Yale - copy, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 1097)
  - Musical Genesis at Yale, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 1098)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine and Photograph, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 1099)
  - Calendar of Events - February, undated (Box 26, Folder 1100)
  - [Yale Publications on Ellington], 1973 (Box 26, Folder 1101)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine - Auditions Ad., 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1102)
  - Yale double page ad., 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1103)
  - Posters for National and International Auditions, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 1104)
  - Tape of Pachelbel Organ - Holland-American Organ Co. - Mr. [Grunnemagh]. Charles Krigbaum, undated (Box 26, Folder 1105)
- Records of the Dean, 1941-2003; Accession 2005-A-038
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2038
  - Dean's Correspondence
    - A, circa 1980-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - B, circa 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - C, circa 1981-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - D, circa 1980-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - E, circa 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - F, circa 1982-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Gilmore, Irving, circa 1974-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - G, circa 1981-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - H, circa 1980-1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - J, circa 1982-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - K, circa 1980-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - L, circa 1980-1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Paul Mellon, 1977-1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Mininberg, Ian, 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - M, circa 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Philip Nelson, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - N, circa 1981-1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - O, circa 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - P, circa 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - R, circa 1981-1993 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - S, circa 1980-1995 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Taylor, Billy Ellington Medal, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - T, circa 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - V, circa 1983-1992 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Jazz Weekend, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - The White House, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - W, circa 1981-1994 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Z, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - DEAN'S SUBJECT FILES
    - AAV, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - A.A.U.P., 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - ACE, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - ACUCAA, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - AIMS, 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - AME, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - AMS: Annual Meeting Denver, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - ASCAP, 1974-1984 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - ASOL, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - American Choral Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - American Music Center, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - American Symphony Orchestra League, 1980 (Box 2)
    - BMI, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - College Music Society, 1972-1990 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Connecticut Department of Education, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - CT. State Music Teachers Assoc., 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - General Professional Organizations, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Institute of International Education, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Institute of Sacred Music, 1973-1993 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Library Expenses, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Library: General, 1975-1987 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Library Gifts, 1960-1986 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Danish Music Collection, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Duane Andrew Davidson Collection, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Mayra Freund Music Collection, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Horowitz Archive, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Herman Langiner Collection, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Nicolas Nabokov papers, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Plamenac Collection, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Hilda Somers Papers, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Tchereprin, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Weill, Kurt/Lenja, Lotte Archive, 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Historic Sound Recordings, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Music Library Assoc. Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Music Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Meet the Composer, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - YSM: Office and Staff Responsibilities, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - New York Philharmonic Music Assistance Fund, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - MMA-DMA, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - International Music Conference September 1975 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Music Educators National Conference (MENC), 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - The National Alliance of Business, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Sanford Medal, 1975-1983 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Sanford Guests and Fellows, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Potential Sanford Guests, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Sanford Guests, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Sanford, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Leon Solecki (Sanford Medal), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Piano Accompanists -Possible, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Theory Possibilities, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Yale Band: Sousa Concert Carnegie Hall Recording, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Chamber Music, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Yale Chamber Players Tour, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Italian -American Historical Society, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - J.F. Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Maiz (New Haven + Yale -Band), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Chamber Orchestra of New England, 1978-19982 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - New Haven Historical Society WPA Festival, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Neighborhood Music School Board, 1976-1981 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Neighborhood Music School, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - NHSO, 1980-1988 (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - New Haven Symphony Board: Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Norfolk
      - 1972-1981 (Box 4, Folder 155)
      - 1972-1987 (Box 4, Folder 156)
      - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 157)
      - 1978 -1980 (Box 4, Folder 158)
      - 1980 (Box 4, Folder 159)
      - 1981 (Box 4, Folder 160)
      - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 161)
      - 1985 (Box 4, Folder 162)
      - 1987-1988 and Summer 1988 (Box 4, Folder 163)
      - 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 164)
      - 1994 (Box 4, Folder 165)
      - Audit, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 166)
      - Winter Use of, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - St. John's
      - 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 168 - 170)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 171)
      - 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 172)
      - Applicants, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 173)
      - Brochure, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 174)
      - Santa Fe Proposal, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Seven Springs Center, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Seven Springs, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Seven Springs, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Seven Springs, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Dallas -NASM, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Seattle, Washington NASM, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Dearborn, Michigan NASM, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - NASM
      - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 183)
      - 1985 (Box 4, Folder 184)
      - 1986 (Box 4, Folder 185)
      - 1987 (Box 4, Folder 186)
      - 1989 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - SESAC, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Organs -Divinity School, 1974-1983 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Buildings, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Building and Grounds Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Facilities, 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Floor Plans -Hendrie, Stoeckel, Sprague, Woolsey, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Building, 1959-1985 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Sprague Hall, 1982-1988 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Stoeckel Hall, 1981-1988 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Hendrie Hall, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Woolsey Hall, 1975-1995 (Box 5, Folder 199 - 201)
    - Woolsey Hall Dome 3rdFloor, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Organs: Woolsey, 1941-1984 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Organs, General, 1972-1988 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Chicago Symphony General, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - NASM
      - Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 207)
      - 1988 (Box 5, Folder 208)
      - Trinity Univ., 1987 (Box 5, Folder 209)
      - 1987 (Box 5, Folder 210)
      - California State, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 211)
      - Albertus Magnus College, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 212)
      - UCLA, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 213)
      - U. Cal. Santa Cruz, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 214)
      - U. Southern California, 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 215)
      - The Catholic University of America, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Curtis School of Music, 1972-1986 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Duke U., 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Eastman, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Glassboro State, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Hartt College of Music, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Indiana University, 1973-1986 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Interlochen Center for the Arts, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - International University Arts Exchange, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Juilliard School, 1975-1985 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Manhattan School of Music, 1976-1983 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Manhattanville College, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - McMaster University, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - National Federation of Music Clubs, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - National Humanities Faculty, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 231)